[Vintage Malayalam song playing]
[Vintage Malayalam song continues]
[Musical Night
by Cochin Kalamela]
- Hey, son... Psst!
- Huh?
Here's the orchestra list.
This is the final song.
Don't forget to add my name
at the end of the announcement.
Saji Pattambi, Troupe Manager.
Got it?
- What was that?
- Saji Pattambi!
- Right, right.
- Okay.
- Hey, Razak...
- Yeah?
The visas for the Europe trip arrived.
Good for you, Saji Chetta.
Oh no!
What's wrong?
We submitted 15 passports
for the trip.
But we got visas
for only 14 people.
One person's visa is missing.
Whose visa is it?
[Announcement] Keyboard: Francis.
Francis Chettan is cleared.
Violin: Xavier,
Linto,
Kundara Das.
The entire violin team
has received visas.
Tumba: Joy.
Tumba Joy made it too.
Tabla: Surendran, Chacko.
Even Chacko, the troublemaker,
got through.
Prabhendu on electric guitar.
- Hey, Razak...
- Yeah?
It's Prabhendu who didn't
get the visa.
- And then?
- Huh?!
Okay, okay.
Let me sleep for a bit.
Prabha...
What's going on?
I'm searching for a jacket
to handle the cold in Europe.
My jacket from the US tour
has turned all mouldy.
I have to place the order today
to get it before we leave.
Ah, true, true.
Hey, that room behind
our rehearsal space...
I'm going to use it
for two months, okay?
I'm vacating my current apartment.
So, to store my stuff...
So you already vacated your flat?
What is this? You could've
at least asked me first!
Just a second.
Let me just enter this OTP.
- Wait, wait! Don't enter it!
- 4--
They've cut the electric guitar, man.
You're the only one
who's not coming on the trip!
What?!
And then?
- Who's having the omelette?
- Just keep it here.
How about some
chicken fry for you, sir?
It's our speciality.
We've also got quail fry.
- No need.
- We have pork with Chinese potatoes.
- It's amazing.
- Get going, will you?
He's a Namboothiri (Brahmin).
Pure veg.
Then I'll remove the pork
and get him the Chinese potatoes.
Hey, this isn't some wedding spread
where food keeps coming.
I still have to pay you, right?
Will this idiot go around
asking everyone the same thing?
We don't even have enough budget
for everyone's omelettes.
If budget was a problem,
you should've said it earlier.
You know, adding an omelette to
the dosa gives it a touch of luxury.
I mean the electric guitar here,
not the omelette!
Yeah, I asked them
the exact same thing.
Then, that sponsor guy
sent a message.
Let me find it.
Chetta, one of the investors
pulled out at the last minute.
We can pull through only
if we remove one person.
- So I...
- And also...
Please convey my special apologies
to Prabhendu Ma'am.
Prabhendu "Ma'am"?
Idiot!
Look, Prabha...
Don't think I'm just trying
to make you feel better.
What if this is actually
for the best?
What? Being broke,
homeless for two months, and starving?!
Oh, give me a break!
It's not like you come from
some poor household!
Wouldn't even a tiny bit of
your dad's and brother's puja income
be enough for you
to manage a full Europe tour?
Wasn't it your ego that made you
snap your sacred thread
and choose to live by cutting costs?
If someone loses faith
and becomes an atheist,
that's their personal choice.
That is not ego.
That's confidence.
- No, Prabha... I didn't mean--
- I'm not finished.
To become a truly
passionate musician,
you have to sacrifice
a lot of things.
Just imagine if A.R. Rahman
had played it safe,
packed his lunch every day
and gone to a bank job,
would we have even half the songs
we performed on stage today?
Prabha, I wasn't trying
to argue with you.
What I actually wanted to talk about
was the passion you have.
You're the most talented person
in our troupe.
Have any of these guys
ever played for a movie?
You're the only one they call
for studio recordings, right?
But that only happens
once in a while, right?
Anyway, since your trip is cancelled,
you should attend your father's
70th birthday celebration.
Your elder brother called you
so many times, right?
No, that's not a good idea.
Look...
There's a proven trend of grumpy dads
becoming warm and loving
once they hit 70.
This is your chance to slip in
and stay there for some time.
You can save money
on food and rent, right?
Plus, free WiFi, free laundry!
How great is that?
Hey, son!
Got any quail eggs?
Him and his damn eggs!
Eggs! Eggs! Eggs!
Where do you keep
shoving all these eggs?
So now it's quail eggs
instead of chicken eggs?
Can't you eat a meal
without eggs, huh?
[Radiant at 70
- Neelakandan Namboothiri]
Indu...
I know you won't come.
But still, whenever you're
free, if you come home,
it would make Dad very happy,
even if he doesn't express it.
Even uncle keeps talking
about wanting to see you.
I'm busy.
I'll try.
Passengers getting down at this stop,
please step out.
[Radiant at 70
- Neelakandan Namboothiri]
Hello...
Huh?
Aadi, no.
You'll get hurt.
When was this?
What?
What did you see while passing?
You must stay for lunch, okay?
There's nothing wrong with Dad.
Just stop the car
and read that flex board properly.
Flex boards aren't
just for funerals, you know!
Okay.
What is it, Thulasi?
Your Dad had asked me to let him know
once the water filter service is done.
Ask them to wait for a bit.
I'll tell Dad right after
the Minister leaves.
This is my eldest son, Deepankuran.
He was with me at Sabarimala.
Then I must have seen him.
Do you work with your Dad
at the temple here?
Oh no.
He's always abroad.
He handles only VIP pujas.
He's flying to Kenya tonight.
And from there, to Dubai.
He even moved closer
to the airport for convenience.
And this is his wife.
Where is your younger son?
He'll be late.
- Let's click the photo.
- Alright.
Sir, over here!
Hey, Pappu!
Why are you coming in
from the back, Indu?
There were too many people
at the front, Thulasi Chechi.
Dad was there too.
I just wanted to avoid
creating a scene.
And this way,
I could see Pappu too.
Not Pappu.
You have to call him "Uncle Pappu" now.
When your mother brought him here
from behind the temple,
my child
was only four days old then.
She's studying in fifth grade now.
He really lost all his cheer
after Mom passed away, didn't he?
Not just him...
You did too.
[Sanskrit news plays on radio]
Sigh! How many times do I have to tell him?
Ugh!
Welcome back, Indu!
You know, if you press that
like this after peeing, it sprays water.
It doesn't even take a second.
Why do you have to make
the whole room stink?
We're already peeing
into water, aren't we?
So why flush more water in?
Aha! So uncle's favourite is here!
Indu, I need to leave right away
to catch my flight.
Go take a quick shower,
wear a nice mundu,
and go take care
of things downstairs.
I have a doubt, Uncle.
For the puja in Kenya, ebony twigs
are required for the sacred fire.
That's not easy
to get at the moment.
And we also need
to check in early.
Is there an alternative I can use?
- Isn't it for an auspicious occasion?
- Yes.
Then just use small twigs
from the Bael tree.
That's a relief!
We have Bael in stock.
Okay, so that's sorted.
Want me to bring you anything
from Kenya?
Bring back a Kenyan beauty
for our chronic bachelor here.
Sounds good. Just make sure
she belongs to the Namboothiri clan!
Yeah, right!
High hopes you have!
- Okay. I'll call you, Indu.
- Okay.
- I'll come see you when I'm back.
- Alright, alright.
Deepu Chettan bought
his assistant a car.
I heard he pays him very well, too.
If you still had your sacred thread on,
Deepu would've taken you along.
Had you stayed with Neelakandan,
you would've been the chief priest
of our family temple by now.
Well, it's all because
of the path you chose, isn't it?
At least what I chose...
is something I can feel and hear.
All you have is hype, right?
There's nothing to see or hear.
That's enough.
He's just ignorant!
Forgive this ignorant fool,
O Lord!
And please remind him to flush
after he urinates, O Lord!
Please don't mind!
Rupesh, the owner of the
shop is this madam here.
Oh!
I'm not saying this just because I did it,
but the puja was a big success.
It's all the Lord's blessing.
Correct.
- Sreekutta...
- Yes.
Hare Krishna, Hare Krishna,
Krishna Krishna Hare Hare.
Hmm!
Hare Rama, Hare Rama,
Rama Rama Hare Hare.
Hare Krishna, Hare Krishna,
Krishna Krishna Hare Hare.
Hare Rama, Hare Rama,
Rama Rama Hare Hare.
Hare Krishna, Hare Krishna...
Sreekutta...
You can take it yourself, sir.
I'm not saying this
just because I did it,
but the puja was a big success.
- So?
- So, well...
- Sreekutta...
- Yes.
Just check whether
that broom works.
The broom is in
excellent working condition.
But you'll need to pay me extra
for cleaning.
Don't be so greedy, Sreekutta.
Why shouldn't I be?
Don't I take on
these low-budget pujas for you too?
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Then why were you trying to find
a new assistant instead of me?
No way!
Would I ever do that?
Oh, really?
Just a minute.
Bhasi, that Sreekuttan
is a complete fraud.
Do you know anyone else
who can assist me?
Even if I say all this,
I'm really fond of you.
Of course, I know that,
Rupeshetta!
And that? 500
the madam gave...
I'm keeping it.
Just consider it
my travel expense.
- Huh?
- Yeah.
- Aren't you happy, Rupeshetta?
- Yes.
I'll get going.
I've got work.
- Pavithran...
- Yes?
We need to leave at
4:30 AM tomorrow.
Okay.
Unni, start cutting vegetables
for the Sambar at 3:30 AM.
So where's the feast, Aunty?
In Thrissur.
Oh! You got your bike fixed?
That's great.
- I'll be here for a couple of months.
- Okay.
The 70th birthday feast
was fantastic, Uncle.
I couldn't eat on a banana leaf
because I arrived late.
Come on! Subramanyan Namboothiri's
feast must be eaten on a banana leaf!
It's really embarrassing when you talk
about yourself in the third person, Dad!
Hello!
Give me your phone, Mom.
How's your uncle keeping, Indu?
He's doing well overall.
Only his leg is giving him some trouble.
Hey, do you need a towel?
No need. I showered
before I came.
- I'm heading to the temple pond.
- Okay.
Looking handsome!
What's on Aunty's mobile phone?
I just checked Anagha's WhatsApp status.
I can't see it.
She blocked me
after we broke up.
- Aren't you ashamed?
- Why should I be?
It's not like I'm bothering her.
Even if we're out
in the semifinals,
we still need to know
who wins the cup, right?
And don't step on the snake.
- What?
Ugh! Aren't you ashamed?
- Rupe...
- Yeah?
Do you know of any jobs
that could help me get by
for the next couple of months?
There are many options
in my dad's line of work.
Would you be willing
to serve at feasts?
No, that won't suit me.
Too many people, too much noise...
Do you know
how to grate coconuts?
How about chopping vegetables?
No way! If I hurt my hand,
I won't be able to play the guitar.
Why don't you just
work as my assistant?
As a priest's assistant?
That's not happening.
Didn't you and your brother Deepu
study the Vedas properly together?
Even after all this time,
I haven't learned as much as you.
But I'm still able
to keep it going, right?
But that was ages ago.
I'm not really convinced about
this whole "God" concept anymore.
In that case, are you certain
we'll even be alive tomorrow?
That just comes down to luck.
So why not treat
that luck as God?
Hey, tell them to buy it
only if they really need it!
[in Hindi]
Bhai, this is quality stuff.
Hey, where are
those guys headed?
This has been going on
for a week.
No fire, no smoke.
Must be hardcore stuff!
Here? With me around?
How dare they!
- Rupe...
- I'm not the same Rupa anymore. Move!
Rupe, drop it!
You'll land in trouble!
This is common everywhere!
Just zip it!
Hey! Hey!
Who are you guys? Huh?
What's going on here?
Go on! Go home!
Clear out!
Want me to call the cops?
[In Hindi]
Go, go! Go home!
Say something, man.
Who the hell are you guys?
Look at those jeans,
that bag, that chain!
You better cut that hair
and beard tomorrow!
Just chase this pest away.
Scared?
Me? What for?
Oh no!
No, child!
Don't do that!
I said don't!
Oh, Goddess!
Don't! Oh, Goddess!
- Run!
- I am running!
That child has such perfect aim!
Indu, I am coming!
Take the soap and towel with you.
Okay.
Chetta, that was awesome!
You elevated the song
to the next level.
It's all because of
the Goddess's grace!
- Right, chetta?
- Yes, yes.
Can I just GPay you?
You don't have cash?
Err... Sanaletta...
We don't have cash.
It'll be credited to your account.
Don't worry.
Nice work.
Psst... Psst!
I've told you so many times
not to call me for these
low-budget music albums.
Oh, I see!
You said I should call you
even for a Rs.1000 job.
This one pays Rs.2500.
- Then where is it?
- It'll come when it comes.
I barely have money
to get home, Faizal.
Don't get stressed, Prabha.
Money comes today,
goes tomorrow.
How can it go tomorrow
if it hasn't come today?!
You know the composer
Viraj Trivedi, right?
He's looking for new
electric guitarists from Kerala.
There's a new Malayali girl
in his management team.
That's where this came from.
Remember the session
you did for Justin?
I've already sent it to them!
All his movie and stage-show teams
are from Mumbai.
Photo! Photo!
But it's worth a shot, right?
- What?
- I said, we can try!
Okay.
Is this to check your oxygen level?
It's for credit card verification.
- Want one?
- No, no! It's too stressful!
You can withdraw up to
Rs.60,000 per month, sir.
- Really?
- Yes.
Hell yeah!
Bro, get him one.
What do you do for a living, sir?
I'm a musician.
Oh, then you'll definitely be rejected.
- Huh?!
- Sign here.
Sir, one photo.
Don't smile so much.
Bro!
You got Rs.200?
I went to Ernakulam yesterday
and came back with nothing.
There's zero stock!
How would I have money?!
Why don't you just ask your dad?
Me? Ask him?
Not in this lifetime!
What is it?
Never mind, it's fine.
Who is fine? Me?
Well, not that...
If you have something to say,
just say it.
Do you have change?
How much for?
For... errr... two hundred.
Will two hundreds work?
A single 200 rupee note
is also fine.
Then that isn't really
"change," is it?
Why do you need it?
Just to step out for a while.
Then why don't you just...
step out?
I was thinking
I'd get a tea as well.
Oh...
- One minute.
- Okay.
You recognise us, don't you?
Of course!
I remember seeing your daughter
when she was very young.
She's grown up so much!
Oh no, she's just my neighbour.
When I told her
we were coming here,
she came along
to see your ancestral house.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, sorry!
You both have a son, right?
This is my brother.
My husband is in Qatar.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
Here you go.
There's enough tea
for three cups.
Help yourself
whenever you want.
Okay?
Back in our day, if Father knew
I drank tea from outside,
I'd get beaten instantly.
Kids these days...
they are just different.
That was funny!
Weren't you the first one
to gain fame here, Prahladan Namboothiri?
Even my father
started off as your assistant, right?
So what?
How do you put up with Dad's
attitude and still stay here?
Because I'm very fond of myself.
Huh?!
What do we really want in life?
Someone who loves us dearly,
and takes good care of us.
Right?
Yes.
Why can't I be that person?
I love myself dearly.
And I take very good care of myself.
You don't care about anyone but yourself!
You have no idea what
I'm going through!
[quotes a sloka from the Mahabharata]
What comes next?
Say it out loud.
Don't you know this sloka?
What does it mean?
No crisis can take away
your ability to think.
If you apply that ability,
wealth can be earned again.
Simple.
That's it.
Now go on, earn.
Aunty, where's Rupesh?
He's bathing in our pond.
I don't know why...
He's stopped going to the temple pond.
Rupe...
Yeah?
I'm ready.
Ready for what?
I'm ready to put on
the sacred thread
and perform pujas.
~ The crystal-clear star
in the heavens so bright ~
~ It's holding its solemn vigil
in worshipful light ~
~ To the tune of the soft chant
in gentle sway ~
~ That blooms on the tongue's tip
in a blossoming way ~
~ Within the realm of fading memories
that drift like shade ~
~ The Vedas endure,
refusing to fade ~
~ Counting them one by one
as patterns shift ~
~ Habits change,
letting the unwanted drift ~
~ Not seeing with the outer eyes,
perceiving where the inner soul lies ~
~ Without seeking the safety
of faith's embrace ~
~ On the stylus tip where thought arises,
what counts as truth, what slips as lies ~
~ Don't worry about any of that today,
Just turn to yourself, be yourself your way ~
[Everything is a Delusion]
~ The crystal-clear star
in the heavens so bright ~
~ It's holding its solemn vigil
in worshipful light ~
~ To the tune of the soft chant
in gentle sway ~
~ That blooms on the tongue's tip
in a blossoming way ~
~ Within the realm of fading memories
that drift like shade ~
~ The Vedas endure,
refusing to fade ~
~ Counting them one by one
as patterns shift ~
~ Habits change,
letting the unwanted drift ~
~ In some distant sanctuary
set high in the sky ~
~ Who is there above us
to whom we must bow or comply? ~
~ Is any light greater,
any radiance akin ~
~ Than the fire that blazes brightly,
fiercely within? ~
Seriously? Lighting a match
in a fireworks shop?
~ This is the start,
the time to prepare with heart... ~
~ We must seize the battlefield,
whatever it costs ~
~ We must loosen the tangles,
undo all the knots... ~
~ We must chant the mantra fearlessly,
and must rise to our victory ~
~ Let us move forward,
ahead of the rest ~
~ By your own true being,
Blaze forth as lightning at its best ~
~ As time's own phases onward glide,
as your rituals flow in a faithful tide ~
~ As your deeds take form on life's broad shelf,
discover yourself within your self ~
~ The crystal-clear star
in the heavens so bright ~
~ It's holding its solemn vigil
in worshipful light ~
~ To the tune of the soft chant
in gentle sway ~
~ That blooms on the tongue's tip
in a blossoming way ~
- Indu...
- Yeah?
I just noticed something.
Has your accent changed slightly?
- Is that what has come to pass?
- Yes!
Exactly!
That's our traditional accent.
Does that really matter?
Priest, breakfast is ready.
- Please have it before you leave.
- Is that so?
- Can't we just eat at home later?
- There's only Upma at home.
It's masala dosa here.
I'll be right back.
Oh dear...
Five, six...
6 x 5 = 36...
It's okay.
Move.
This looks good!
- Did you make this, Paulose?
- Yes.
- Is it made of teak?
Paulose insists it's teak.
Then it must've cost a lot.
Anything Paulose builds
never comes cheap, right?
I just hope it's sturdy enough.
It's sturdier than
the wig on your head.
Better hold on to it.
Don't let it fly away.
How many people can
sit on this, Paulose?
It won't move an inch
even if the whole village sits on it.
Stop exaggerating, Paulose!
Me? Exaggerating?
Please step aside, sir.
I'll prove it now!
All of you, move aside.
Come here, son.
You sit there.
All you kids,
go and sit.
Go sit, Chechi.
Go on.
Come on, everyone.
Come and sit.
- What? You want to sit, Priest?
- No, no.
Please sit.
It'll be an honour.
Move aside.
Let the priest sit.
- No, really...
- Go on, sit.
How about now?
Call your dad or mom,
whoever's around.
Let them try swinging on it.
Psst...
Coming?
Come here, big shot!
Give it a good push!
Oh my!
Oh no!
Nothing to worry!
The swing is perfectly fine.
Go on, cry again.
Shush!
Move, move!
Rupe!
Does it hurt, son?
Not at all.
The doctor said the MRI scan showed
nothing wrong with his head.
Such a waste of money!
At least the X-ray
was worth it.
It shows swelling at two spots
on his spine.
Luckily, with Indu around, all the
pujas you agreed to won't be cancelled.
- Yes.
- Hmm.
Now, if you both could step outside.
I need to talk to Indu in private.
Go on.
Go on, Mom!
Let's go.
- Indu...
- Yeah?
Yes, I'm your cousin.
But now...
Now what?
Now I'm your employer too.
So what?
You're fully capable
of doing pujas on your own now,
and making your own money.
That makes me proud.
Look, I'm not planning
to do this forever.
I'll leave once
I'm financially stable.
Sure, you can leave.
That's not my point.
From tomorrow, we split
whatever you earn from the pujas,
fifty-fifty.
Huh?!
But I'm the one
doing the puja!
And I'm the one
bringing in the clients, right?
- Rupe!
- Listen, Indu...
When family and friends
turn into business partners,
having clarity about financial matters
can help prevent future conflicts.
There's no point
spoiling our relationship over it.
That's all I wanted to say.
- 60-40.
- Yeah, that's fine. Fine.
40 is fine, 40 is fine.
You are happy, right?
~ It clears up like the sky
in its vast renew ~
~ It fills like the ocean of milk
breaking through ~
~ Ascend the chariot of that wisdom
alive within you ~
~ And continue your journey,
steady and true ~
~ Every single battle
that comes our way ~
~ Let us face it with
blazing determination each day ~
~ On the stylus tip where thought arises,
what counts as truth, what slips as lies ~
~ Don't worry about any of that today,
Just turn to yourself, be yourself your way ~
~ The crystal-clear star
in the heavens so bright ~
~ It's holding its solemn vigil
in worshipful light ~
~ To the tune of the soft chant
in gentle sway ~
~ That blooms on the tongue's tip
in a blossoming way ~
~ Within the realm of fading memories
that drift like shade ~
~ The Vedas endure,
refusing to fade ~
~ Counting them one by one
as patterns shift ~
~ Habits change,
letting the unwanted drift ~
Prabha...
Just a minute.
- Almost done.
- Okay.
Hey, Prabha...
Faizal told me.
Congrats!
Don't forget us
when you make it big in Bombay!
Oh, come on!
Hey...
I've sent you a
request on Instagram.
I'm not very active on it.
Well, you can just accept it
right now.
Oh... just a minute.
Hey, Rupe...
Indu, where are you?
Remember I told you about
Viraj Trivedi, the Hindi music director?
He loved the track
I sent him.
He has called me to the studio
for a video call session.
Wow, congrats!
That's amazing!
What are you doing
tomorrow evening?
I've got a Ganesha Puja
at Kadampuzha at dawn.
I thought I'd watch a movie
later in the evening.
Ugh! That's a horrible movie!
But I never told you
which movie it was!
Oh, you didn't?
- He didn't!
- Yeah, you didn't.
Anyway, listen...
Can you handle
one more puja tomorrow?
You can go after 6:00 PM.
The pay is huge!
The biggest one our astrologer
Krishnanunni has ever given us!
What kind of puja?
A lawyer from Palakkad...
His son who's a 12th grade student,
is said to be possessed.
He's been seeing and hearing things.
Rupe, I honestly don't know
anything about exorcisms.
Hey, I'll walk you through it.
I'll send you a PDF on WhatsApp
with updated chants and procedures.
Otherwise, it's the same
Sudarshana Homam setup.
Just add more fire and flowers
for extra punch.
Sometimes I wonder why we named
you 'Rupe'. You're obsessed with money.
How is that my fault?
Hey... please!
Alright.
- And hey, don't forget... 60-40.
Yeah, okay.
Hey Prabha...
Sorry, man. Not today.
Viraj sir's manager just called.
He worked through the night
and is sleeping during the day.
Okay.
That's fine.
Just keep me posted next time.
Okay?
Okay.
So...
Can you add my Insta ID now?
Chokichosky.
Chokay... I mean, okay.
[Straight from the heart]
If you're going for physiotherapy,
use the car.
Ha! It's such a struggle for me
to climb down into that low car
and then haul myself back up.
An auto rickshaw is far
more comfortable.
Don't you have a puja today?
Yes.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
What, am I supposed
to drive it myself now?
Hey, what's all this
you've been chopping off?
Will you destroy all the plants?
For the plants,
this is just like a haircut.
They might even
be enjoying it.
I'm crazy about plants, you know.
Shall we go?
Name?
Hibiscus rosa-sinensis.
It's also called "China Rose".
Not that!
What's your name?
Oh!
I'm Animon.
- Ready to go?
- Yeah, let's go.
Feel free to take the car
when you go for your pujas.
It's okay.
I'll just go in this auto.
What puja is happening
so late, sir?
Is it for the Goddess?
No! It's an exorcism.
- Advocate Dileep?
- Yes.
Rupesh had called.
Need a hand with your supplies?
No, it's fine.
I have someone with--
I'll call the driver.
Can I keep this here?
Yes, please.
Just the grass mat is left, right?
Yes, that's it.
- You can bring the boy in 10 minutes.
- Okay.
Deepthi Chechi!
Here you go.
It'll be ready in 10 minutes.
Alright.
Do you practice
at the District Court here?
Yes, for the past two months.
- I'm from Kuttikkanam.
- I see.
Whose guitar is that?
That's Kuttu's.
Ah... I mean, Avinash.
He plays really well.
He always says,
"I'm hungry, Latha Chechi."
Now, he has zero appetite.
Oh.
Didn't you take him
to a doctor?
We did. There's a doctor
at NIMHANS.
Dr. Raphael.
He's brilliant.
We consulted him.
Kuttu is on medication too.
But my wife insisted
on having this puja done.
I don't really believe in any of this.
You can sit.
Kutta... Sit down, son.
Sit down.
You can sit with him, Ma'am.
That will make him
more comfortable.
Sit down, son.
When did all this begin?
It's been about a week now.
One night, he walked into our room crying
and lay down beside us.
He says someone keeps approaching him,
trying to say something.
A man or a woman?
It's a young girl.
Now he needs me with him 24/7.
Even when he goes
to the bathroom!
Hello!
He makes no eye contact at all now.
I see.
We're about to begin the puja.
The spiritual reading suggests
this is a case of possession.
Once this puja is complete,
the spirit will leave his body
and merge with the supreme.
Hi Latha Chechi...
Huh?
Kuttu! Oh, my son!
- Latha, are you seeing this?
It worked?
Dileepetta!
That's not possible!
- Look, our son!
- Hey, Kuttu! Are you okay?
Yeah, I am okay.
Deepthi!
See? Didn't I tell you?
- Gho...
Go on, say it.
You go ahead.
The ghost is definitely gone.
All the chants I sent you
worked like a charm.
Oh, come on! They had already
consulted a doctor.
I think the medicine
finally kicked in.
Oh...
Still, if that lawyer paid Rs.1 lakh
instead of the Rs.60,000 we asked...
- Indu...
- What?
Ever since you started wearing
the sacred thread and doing pujas,
don't you feel some
kind of divine presence?
I see this as
a job I'm paid for.
So shouldn't I just be sincere,
stay disciplined,
and do the job I was hired for
as honestly as I can?
- You should.
- That's what this 'presence' means to me.
Oh.
I'm leaving.
And I need a three-day break,
starting day after tomorrow.
Oh no, no, no!
I've already scheduled
three pujas for you!
- Take your break after that.
- No! No way!
How about 60-40?
- 70-30.
- Okay.
Mom, give me your phone.
She hasn't posted
any status update today!
Oh.
Hello?
There are several types of
silver idols here for today's ritual.
I've sent you the photos.
Which one should I get?
Oh, just a second.
Get the smallest one.
Okay, okay.
I'll take this one.
By the way, who's that Chinese fellow
in your WhatsApp DP?
Chinese fellow?
He's a Korean singer.
Oh, I see.
For a moment, I thought
I'd called the wrong person.
- Alright then.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Okay.
Hello.
You're Prabhendu, aren't you?
I'm Sreekuttan.
I used to be
Rupeshettan's assistant.
Oh!
Rupeshettan used
to talk about a cousin
who left home twelve years ago,
threw away his sacred thread, and has
been wandering around playing the guitar.
So that's you, huh?
And on top of that, you're an atheist!
Good heavens!
Let's keep this between us.
So what if I charge a little extra?
You're better off with me by your side.
Okay, right?
Yes, we're okay!
Oh dear...
What just happened?
He must be hurt.
Move, move.
- Are you hurt?
- You're okay, right?
- Hello!
- Is he okay?
Oh Goddess!
If I've done anything wrong
without meaning to,
please forgive me, Priest.
Let's go.
Chechi, are you Prabhendu?
- Huh?
- I asked if you're Prabhendu.
- No. Why?
- I have a parcel for Prabhendu.
- Give it to me.
- To you?
- What's the problem?
- Go call Prabhendu Chechi.
I'll hand it over to her myself.
Not Chechi.
He's a Chettan.
- Chettan?
- Yes.
Alright. Go call him then.
I'll make sure
the crows don't peck it.
Wait here.
There's a parcel for you, Indutty.
For me?
What could it be?
I haven't ordered anything!
Maybe you've got the wrong address.
Prabhendu N. Namboothiri,
Mullasseri House.
That's you, right?
- Yeah.
- Here you go.
But I don't even have your app
on my phone...
It's there, right?
You'll get an OTP.
Can you read it out?
- 6, 2, 0...
- 4, 0, 9.
- Okay.
- Wait, what about the payment?
That's already done.
Payment was through credit card.
Credit card?
But I never added my credit card to--
So that's saved too?
This is clearly a mistake.
Please return this.
I can't just take it back.
I need a return token
from the company.
That'll take a couple of days.
I swear, I didn't order this.
Sir, if you have a complaint,
take your time
and call customer care.
That's what they're there for, right?
What's going on with your phone?
You've been glued to it for a while.
I'm just deleting some unnecessary apps
from my phone, Uncle.
The WhatsApp photo keeps
changing on its own!
It's downloading apps on its own
and ordering clothes with my credit card!
Must be some Chinese app.
Did you lose any money?
Yup.
I've requested a refund.
Hopefully it comes through.
Hi!
Hey, don't panic.
I'll go and come back later.
Bye!
Why did you sleep here last night?
What's with this sudden affection?
I had a dream last night.
It really shook me.
Oh!
There was a girl...
She was just sitting there, staring at me.
A very beautiful girl.
That's a standard dream for bachelors
well past their marriage age.
Even at my age,
I get such dreams.
So naturally, you would too!
This wasn't like that.
I even heard her voice clearly.
She said,
"I'll go and come back later."
This is a 90-year-old
ancestral home, right?
All sorts of things can show up here.
Damn!
I've been available right next
door for all these years,
and not a single one
ever came to see me!
Nah, this one seems pretty modern.
She didn't even try to scare me.
She was just sitting there casually,
scrolling through my phone.
Next time you see her,
send her my way.
At least I'll have some company.
Hey, call Paul and ask him
to send an autorickshaw.
I've got a meeting at ten.
Okay.
Hi!
Good morning.
Please, come in.
Come on in.
Kuttoos had an Android phone, you know.
I was never really
comfortable with Android.
The fact that you have an iPhone
is such a relief, Prabha!
Which 'Kuttoos'?
Remember the puja you did that day?
What was his real name again?
Oh... Avinash!
Gosh, he was such a cutie!
But scared out of his mind.
So scared,
he wouldn't even make eye contact!
How are you supposed to talk to someone
who won't even look at you?
But you're very brave, Prabha.
You have good eye contact.
I like it.
Ten on Ten!
But you did get scared yesterday.
It's totally understandable.
Anyone would have been scared.
It was your first time, right?
By the way, is it okay
if I call you Prabha?
Sure.
I noticed your friends calling
you that in your chats.
Also, it's such an interesting name.
Prabhendu.
Super sweet.
I like it.
- I really like it.
- Indu!
- I need the auto rickshaw
only at 11 o'clock.
- I just read the notice.
Okay!
Alright, you can have
your phone back now.
I don't need it again till the night.
Anxiety?
Bipolar?
No.
Then what on earth is it?
Huh?!
I was talking to her.
It's not dry yet.
Can you please call Doctor Raphael?
That's me.
What's the matter?
So... I'm a person who performs pujas.
Three days ago,
I went to a house for a puja.
- Not a house, actually a flat, for puja--
- Stop, Stop!
Could you please move, Chechi?
- Continue.
- Like I said, I perform pujas.
Three days ago,
I went to a flat for a puja.
It was meant to drive out a spirit.
His parents said they had
brought him to you, Doctor.
Avinash.
He's slightly chubby...
Oh, yes!
Anyway, after the puja,
he recovered completely.
But now I'm experiencing
the same symptoms he had.
I'm seeing the same girl
he said he used to see.
I saw her last night,
and again today, in broad daylight.
I could hear her voice too.
Crystal clear.
Can you see her right now?
Not right now.
And?
Well, that's all.
Also, the moment I saw that boy,
I understood what the issue was.
Seeing people who aren't there,
hearing voices nobody else hears...
Sheezo-phrenia!
Schizophrenia.
I Googled it
and I have all the symptoms.
- You Googled it?
- Yeah.
I'm willing to take any medication.
Am I talking too fast right now?
Doctor, are you following me so far?
Didn't you say you fixed
Avinash's problem with your puja?
- Yes.
- Then similarly...
why not perform a puja
and cure your own condition?
I...
I don't believe in God, Doctor.
I'm...
an atheist.
Huh?!
Then how can you be doing pujas?
Well...
I'm basically a musician.
A guitarist.
I'm on a short break right now.
I was trained in all these rituals
until I turned nineteen.
When did you begin
losing faith in this "item"?
Which "item," Doctor?
God.
Well... that...
Come with me.
One day, it was just my mother
and me at home.
My brother, father, and uncle
had gone to Delhi for a puja.
Mom and I were watching
an A.R. Rahman concert on Doordarshan.
Mom had Master's degree in Music.
She even played the veena.
We have a shrine inside the house,
almost like a small temple.
When it was time
to do the puja there,
I purified myself and went inside.
We call it the 'Thevaram'.
Just as I lit the lamp
and began the Puja,
I heard my mother
calling out to me loudly.
I ignored it.
I thought I would
finish the puja first.
When I went back,
I saw my mom lying face down
on the floor, next to the sofa.
The moment I held her,
I knew she was gone.
It was a cardiac arrest.
I held my mom in my lap
and stared right at the lamp,
still burning after the puja.
I could see it clearly
from where I was.
That day,
more than sadness,
what I felt was anger.
In that moment,
I lost my connection with God.
Man, this is your real issue!
You have deep-seated trauma.
No way.
Those two things
have nothing to do with each other.
Whether they're connected or not,
let's deal with this trauma first.
What if that girl
shows up again?
Let her show up.
She'll go away
the same way she appeared.
I'll give you a simple fix for that.
There's a tablet
that contains melatonin.
It's not a sleeping pill.
Just take it
before you go to bed.
You will get a good sleep.
Huh?
Don't I need any other medicine?
There's no better medicine in the world
than a good night's sleep.
Trust me.
You're fine.
Okay.
You are okay!
Hi!
I didn't want to wake you up,
so I just came and sat here quietly.
Anyway, I'm glad
I saw you today.
Why should we keep
startling each other like this?
We're well past that stage now,
aren't we?
Whoa! Relax.
This isn't a dream.
Look, the time is 1:40 AM.
Uncle just went to the wash room
and got back in bed.
As usual, he didn't flush.
Shall I flush it for him?
I can do it from here.
Shall I turn on the light?
Sorry, I'm just figuring this out.
You just need to change the bulb.
Indu!
I think he got up.
Tell you what.
You go back to sleep.
You've taken the medicine, right?
And if you don't mind,
I need to check some stuff on this.
I'll return it in the morning.
What was that sound?
Oh! He can't see me.
Your uncle can't see me.
Oh!
What do you mean, 'Oh'?
I asked what that sound was.
Oh, that...
I think the bulb blew
from a voltage surge.
My dear Indu,
just say your prayers
and go to sleep.
No faith in God,
but scared out of your wits!
Ugh!
Go back to sleep, Prabha.
I'm okay out here.
By the way, good call on placing
the return request for the kurta.
I ordered the white kurta
with lavender accents.
But I think they sent
white with pink instead.
Anyway, I've scheduled
the pickup for tomorrow.
Just make sure
you hand it over.
Is there something
you want to ask me?
Finally!
Go on, ask me.
Who... are you?
I hate to say this.
But I think I'm a ghost.
Yeah, I think so.
Pradeep...
July 12th and 13th
are auspicious days.
Plan it accordingly.
Okay?
What are you doing here
at this hour?
What's in the bag?
Psst... psst!
Don't! Don't!
[chants slokas]
Psst... psst!
Over here!
Where did you see it?
In my room.
- It's still here.
- Still there?
Why didn't you tell me
this when you called?
- But my phone is with her!
- Oh.
Come on.
Will she hurt me?
- I don't think so.
- You don't "think" so?
Why is this door locked?
So she can't get out.
Oh.
The ghost? Seriously?
Open it.
And that?
Open that too!
She's gone!
Didn't I tell you, Indu?
It's just your mind playing tricks.
The rest will sort itself
out after the puja.
You know who's doing it, right?
East should be this side, right?
- That side.
- Right.
No, I'll handle this.
Right now, you're the client.
- You've got a lamp?
- Yes.
Bring it here.
I need to light it.
I'll handle that as well.
Once you conquer fear,
the battle is half-won...
Hey! Where are you off to?
You asked me to bring the lamp.
Don't go alone.
I'll come with you.
Oil, coconut, matches...
Take everything at once.
Don't keep going in and
out while I'm inside.
It isn't safe.
What are you staring at?
Let's go!
My god, I've never
seen anyone so scared!
Phew! Safe!
Uncle, I've come to collect
a parcel for return.
What parcel?
It's a kurta set.
But nobody in this
house wears kurtas.
This one is a ladies' kurta.
Prabhendu must be your son, right?
- Yes.
- Ah, he ordered it.
- Here you go.
- Right!
Indutty gave it to
me in the morning.
Valentine's Day is
around the corner, right?
Must be a gift for someone special.
Oh dear, this Indutty!
Phew!
I'm not just saying this
because I did it...
- What?
- The puja was a big success.
Hmm.
That thing you spoke about...
She's a real terror.
I watched her leave
with my own eyes!
Hmm.
I'm thinking maybe
I should see that doctor again.
Come on!
What for?
This is a form of treatment too.
This time, I decided to add
a touch of extra sorcery,
just for flavour.
And it worked perfectly.
Why do you look so unconvinced?
No, I'm not doubting anything.
Alright then! Get up.
Oh my...
Let me know once you're
done being scared.
There are a few pending pujas.
Let's wrap those up too.
Alright then, I'll get going.
- Okay.
- I forgot something.
Your father is upset that you
don't visit the temple anymore.
At least go once in a while.
Poor soul.
What are you thinking?
That item?
She's gone!
Chill! Okay?
Let me see how she
dares to return now!
Okay.
Huh!
Done getting shocked?
Who's he calling an "item"?
Do I look like an item?
Don't go without talking to me.
If you keep running away,
that's all you'll ever do.
Listen... have I done anything to you
like those horror-movie ghosts?
Yes or no?
No.
Other than you getting
shocked seeing me
and me getting shocked
seeing you,
have I troubled you in any way?
Yes or no?
No.
Look, I don't have
clarity on this either.
I don't even know what happened to me.
And... I have no clue
why I'm following you around
as if we're connected
via Bluetooth.
Do you even realise
how hard this is for me?
Huh?
It's just that...
you didn't ask yes or no.
For the love of Jesus,
don't be scared of me!
It makes me feel guilty
for no reason.
Jesus?
Huh?
So, you're a Christian?
Oh! Yeah.
Oh!!
No wonder!
Do you sell crosses here?
What's the purpose?
For...
protection.
Protection from what?
No, no... just general safety.
Safety from what exactly?
For my own peace of mind, Chetta.
Wood or metal?
Which one is more powerful?
This isn't a lightbulb
you pick by wattage.
That depends on your faith.
Lali!
Yes?
Show him the crosses.
Are you Roman Catholic?
No.
Oh, from the Jacobite Church then.
Err...
No.
Mar Thoma church, then?
Mar...
Yes.
- Huh?
- Yes, you're right.
Ah, I knew it!
The moment I saw you,
I knew you were
a proper Mar Thoma boy.
- Yes.
- Right.
So, pick whichever one
you like. Okay?
So, this should clear things up, right?
I mean, I'm literally standing
surrounded by crosses right now.
Including you.
Hey! If Jesus had a problem with me,
wouldn't I be gone by now?
Look, I honestly don't know
how I became a ghost,
or why I am one,
or how to stop being one.
And you know
what's the funny part?
I can't remember
a single important detail!
I can't even recall my name!
Answer it.
- Faizal...
- Hey, Prabha...
Wherever you are, drop everything
and get to the studio by midnight.
Viraj sir said he'll
join on a video call.
He wants to test you
for a track in his next film.
I'm kind of stuck right now.
Can we reschedule?
Don't be an idiot, Prabha!
If you miss this now,
there won't be another chance.
I've given Saadhya my word.
Stop stalling and get here.
It's 5:00 PM already.
- I'll be there.
- Okay.
I heard that.
Congrats.
Ah! Come in, come in.
I didn't take the bike,
in case it rained tonight.
Caught a direct bus.
It was pretty comfortable.
You don't mind me
eating non-veg, do you?
Not at all.
I think I'll order a dosa.
I'll order for you, man.
You haven't eaten yet?
How about podi masala dosa?
Yeah.
Who are you looking for?
Oh, nothing.
I asked if podi masala dosa is okay.
Yeah, that's fine.
Dude, hold on.
Saadhya's calling.
Hello, Saadhya...
Yeah.
He's logged in already?
No, no problem.
We're coming.
Dude, Viraj sir has already logged in.
Come on, hurry up!
What about my dosa?
I'm ditching my biriyani, and you're
worried about your dosa? Move!
Prabha, ready.
He's here.
Hi Faizal. All good?
Hi, sir. All good, sir.
All good.
The guitarist. Is he ready?
What's his name?
Prabhendu, sir.
Prabhendu.
Shall I call him here, sir?
No, no. No need.
I can hear what he plays, right?
Yeah, of course. Of course.
Okay then.
Let's start now.
Hey...
Sir has composed a new track.
He needs a guitar groove for it.
Kill it!
Faizal, I need a catchy
riff for the melody.
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Prabha... 2-bar cue.
Yeah, okay.
No, no.
Stop, stop.
Prabhendu, I don't want that.
It's not sounding good.
Try some strumming.
Prabha, don't try anything
too fancy.
Just stick to your comfort zone.
Okay.
No, no, no.
What are you doing, man?
Feel the melody and try again.
Faizal, give him a shorter cue.
Sure. Sure, sir.
Prabha, what's wrong with you?
Let's go. Ready.
Okay.
Take.
Stop, stop, stop.
This is not even close!
Faizal, what is this?
I already have people in Mumbai
who play like this.
I want that magic!
We shouldn't waste our time.
Let's look for someone else.
He just can't do it.
Just follow the melody.
Huh?!
What is it, man?
Oh, it's nothing.
Prabha, focus only on the melody.
It's that simple.
Play this.
Prabha...
What do I do?
- Ready.
- Okay, man.
Sir... One last time, sir?
Okay, try.
Okay, sir.
Thank you, thank you.
Prabha, take.
Oh, nice!
I like it!
Faizal, this is exactly what I want!
Thank you, sir.
Prabha, that's brilliant.
Stick with that.
Super. Add one more layer.
Faizal, turn up the reverb.
I'll add one more layer.
Ready!
Too good, man!
Continue!
Too good!
Faizal, call him!
I want to see him.
Sure, sir.
Prabha, come over here.
Sir wants to see you.
You killed it, man!
You just made the tune better,
Prabhendu.
We will do the full song together
in Mumbai.
Thank you, sir.
Perfect!
Faizal, I'll ask Saadhya to coordinate.
Okay.
Your destination is on the left.
Hey! Kiddo!
Hey, look at that.
To be honest,
I didn't quite get that initially.
Great!
And then?
That's exactly what I was thinking.
I know music, and I know
how guitar chords work.
Oh Jesus!
Kuttoos was a guitarist too!
Music connects the three of us!
Strange!
Also, you're an acoustic guy?
Electric Guitar is my favourite.
But people like Viraj sir
usually prefer acoustic
when they're composing.
Ah, I see.
Looks like you've lost your
fear and found some guts.
The fear is gone,
but the confusion remains.
Just relax, Prabha.
I think I'm just delulu.
Alright. So, delulu...
Ordering things online--
Delulu means delusion.
Seeing things that don't exist.
What's the Malayalam word
for delusion?
The Malayalam word for delusion...
"Delulu" works.
Actually, it's cute.
You can just call me Delulu
from now on.
- Delulu!
- Delulu...
Can you please stop ordering
all these clothes?
I'm a little short on cash right now.
Let me explain why, Prabha.
I remember every outfit
I used to wear.
But my favourite kurti...
The white one with
lavender flowers on it...
I simply can't wear that one now.
So I thought, maybe I
could wear it if I saw it.
Oh.
Hey...
Can you conjure up
a 500 rupee note?
Hey! I'm not some genie
you summon from a bottle!
I can handle a few simple things.
I have some skills.
Like last week, when that guy acted smart
with you, and I made his bike crash.
Stuff like that.
Which guy? Sreekuttan?
I don't know his name.
Oh my God!!!
Oh, sorry!
Not God, not God.
Actually, I do remember
certain things about myself.
Like my lifestyle, my habits,
my interests.
But I can't remember
any of the main things.
Like my family,
or my friends...
Nothing at all!
Except for one thing.
What's that?
Right before I died,
someone, somewhere, said "Yes."
It's like someone wanted me to die.
Who was it?
I don't know.
Well... I meant to say this
back at the studio.
You have a beautiful voice, Delulu.
You're gifted.
If you hadn't died...
you would've become a star.
Now that I'm dead,
becoming a star is my only option, right?
~ When someone sat close to me at night,
like new-fallen rain in cool delight ~
~ My heart shifted, lighter than ever,
turning at once to a moonlit river ~
~ Slowly unfolding its wings
in tender delight ~
~ Weaving a chain of laughter
pure and bright ~
~ My mind fills up
on its own tonight ~
~ Come, let's go to distances
we've never seen ~
~ Becoming two lovely,
colourful clouds serene ~
~ In this new birth
where our paths convene ~
~ Let's find our shelter on a blossom
branch kissed by morning dew ~
~ Becoming the breath
that rises soft and true ~
~ Till every painful memory
softens and bids adieu ~
Stop!
~ From which stretch of sky
did I fall and fly ~
~ A lost little star
slipping out of the sky? ~
~ Who else must I search for
as days drift by? ~
~ I still don't know
the right paths to surmise ~
~ Yet I carried a deep desire
for a safe haven's rise ~
~ Which lingered as moisture
gently filling my eyes ~
~ In all this rush
that surrounds me endlessly ~
~ Isn't there someone nearby
who cares for me? ~
~ Even at my lightest mischief,
soft and carefree ~
~ Doesn't he keep smiling,
happily? ~
~ Will you join your hands
and shape a swing? ~
~ If you do, I will step forward with joy
and gently begin to swing ~
~ When someone sat close to me at night,
like new-fallen rain in cool delight ~
~ My heart shifted, lighter than ever,
turning at once to a moonlit river ~
~ Slowly unfolding its wings
in tender delight ~
~ Weaving a chain of laughter
pure and bright ~
~ My mind fills up
on its own tonight ~
[Astrologer: Krishnanunni Panicker]
So you just want me to visit
the houses you're trying to sell?
Not every one of them, Rupe.
Only the ones where
unnatural deaths have happened.
Yes, houses where notorious murders
have occurred.
And suicides.
Altogether,
I've got nearly 28 such houses
on hold across Kerala.
Will one puja take care
of all of them?
Not like that. First, I will do
an astrological assessment
and then determine
the required remedies.
After that, you just have to
carry them out.
Your learned cousin is the one
who went for the lawyer's
son's puja that day, right?
He's very skilled.
It'd be great if he came too.
No chance!
Prabhendu works only part-time.
He only deals with
cases involving children.
Risky cases like these
are handled by me personally.
Yes, what is it?
I'm looking for the office
of the family court lawyer.
Is it a mutual divorce?
No. I'm okay with it.
But my wife is the one
who wants to end it.
That's something
we can resolve right here.
Still, go meet the lawyer.
- It's the office next door.
- Okay.
So, what about the payment?
What if there's more than one ghost in
those houses where mass murders occurred?
That depends.
We'll even leave some
room for you to negotiate.
If that's the case... err...
a per-head rate for each ghost.
- Isn't it okay?
- Okay.
Okay!
Lord Guruvayurappa!
Just hold this
and give it one pull.
Wow, this is so easy!
Also, no tears wasted.
- Thulasi!
Your dad!
Grab Pappu's blue spray
from the kitchen.
Or never mind.
I'll come there.
Okay.
Indutty...
Your dad is coming.
Get going. I'll call you
when lunch is ready.
Huh?!
You're here?
Who is in there then?
It... it...
it's from the speaker, Uncle.
Then how did it stop now?
Oh, really?
Let me check.
Hey, don't pull these kinds of stunts
when I'm not around.
Sorry!
I thought you had grand plans
for cooking today?
What happened?
Finished helping her already?
Well... it's just...
Dad was there with Pappu.
So I just came back inside.
By the way, why aren't you two
talking to each other?
What's the reason?
It's because of Pappu.
What did Pappu do?
Well...
The day my mom passed away...
everyone was here.
It was chaotic,
with all the crying and commotion.
When it was time
to take her body away,
Pappu suddenly started
barking non-stop.
Mom was his favourite person.
He was tied up
in the backyard then.
So I hurried out
and brought him inside.
He deserved to see Mom
one last time, right?
The moment Dad saw him,
he shouted,
"Both of you, get out!"
Dad never liked animals.
He wouldn't even look at Pappu.
I took him and stood outside...
until all the rituals were over.
Dad took away...
the last chance for me
and Pappu...
to be with Mom.
From that day on,
I've barely spoken to him.
And neither has Dad, not since I removed
my sacred thread.
But that was back then, right?
Now you've got
your sacred thread again,
and your Dad is now
Pappu's favourite person.
Then why aren't you two talking?
It's not possible now.
We just... got set that way.
Then just reset it!
Look, Prabha...
staying upset with someone
and holding onto it forever...
it's simply exhausting.
Life's too short for all that!
Hmm.
Point.
Thank you.
Errr...
I'm on the phone, Uncle.
Thulasi has called
us to have lunch.
Come on.
- Yes, I'll be there.
I'll tell Indu.
Alright.
- Was that Neelakandan?
- Yes.
Deepu chettan has come home,
along with everyone.
He called to ask if Indu
will attend the temple festival.
Uncle is hesitant
to ask him directly.
Indu had lunch, took his bike,
and went off somewhere.
Is that so?
Uncle...
Has Indu been acting
a little unusual lately?
- Ha! I was just about to ask you that.
- Oh really?
- One thing's certain.
- What?
- He's possessed.
- By a ghost?
Not a ghost!
Possessed by love for a girl!
How do you know?
I caught him red-handed today.
He was whispering away
on the phone.
From the looks of it,
it was definitely a girl
on the other end.
Oh! I had no idea!
There's a lot
you've got no idea about!
Do you even know
all the puja rituals?
Well,
you should've thought of that when
you got your sister married to a cook!
The fact that I made it this far
from that background
is purely because of my own talent!
That much I'll accept.
Uncle...
I'm thinking of
focusing on exorcisms.
There are families that have been
doing that for generations, Rupe.
To avoid the side effects,
you need the expertise and spiritual energy
passed down through generations.
I'm doing this after proper study.
So I'm not scared.
- Fear is a good thing!
- Huh?!
Fear was the very first emotion
humans ever had...
for basic safety.
I do follow basic safety precautions
when I perform exorcisms.
There are three types of spirits.
Do you know?
Hmm. I don't.
Randukama...
Bhokthukama...
and Handukama.
The first two are relatively harmless.
But the Handukama
comes only to kill!
It won't go back
without taking a life.
Oh god!
Annamma Joseph.
Born in 1932.
Not this one either.
Delulu!
Here's one...
a girl named Tessa.
Born in '88.
Try to remember...
Could your name be Tessa?
No! Born in '88 means
she's over 30!
How old do I look to you?
About twen--
Thirty-thirty two!
What?! I'm not that old!
Are there any other
Mar Thoma churches around here?
Let's see... around here...
If you're a ghost
who's crossed districts,
we might have to check
the Kottayam-Thiruvalla area.
It's alright.
We'll keep looking.
Lillykutty!
I just wish I could at
least remember my name.
Don't worry, Delulu.
We will keep trying.
Won't we, Lillykutty?
- Did you know my grandmother?
- Huh?
I asked whether you knew my grandmother.
Yes... your grandmother...
I went to her tuition
classes back in eighth grade.
Don't you recognize us?
Yes, I do.
Kalarickal Davis...
the one who lives near the tile factory?
Of course!
Davis Chettan is like family to us!
I am Davis!
Davis Chetta...
Are there any other
new cemeteries nearby?
Cemetery?
There's St. George Cemetery.
I already went there.
Anything else, dear?
Then... there's Paleparambil...
Did you go to Paleparambil Church?
Yeah, I went there too.
There are no other cemeteries.
None, huh?
Hmm, alright then.
Okay, get up.
Let's go.
Okay.
Come on.
You look really beautiful after switching
from that T-shirt to a churidar.
Rupe! Where's Indu?
I brought him.
But he didn't come inside.
Go check on him, Rupe.
Ask him to come and be here.
Okay, Deepu Chetta.
That's Animon for you!
My turn.
Don't miss.
You see that teddy bear? That's the prize.
I need it for my autorickshaw.
Wait and watch!
It didn't pop?
Not even close!
Guess I've lost my teddy bear.
Just a minute.
Psst!
One single shot.
Make it pop, okay?
- Okay.
What?
You called me, didn't you?
Err... it's just...
balloon...
It didn't pop.
- Huh?
- Sorry.
Don't worry.
No one saw it except me.
My prestige is
on the line here, okay?
It has to pop
on the count of three.
Done.
One...
Two...
Sorry!
[Traditional satirical storytelling
performance on stage]
Bless you!
You stole it already?!
Ugh! No!
I just need one good look
at someone.
I can wear it.
How do I look?
Hmm... not bad.
A little appreciation would be nice.
I have to feel like it, right?
Hey, you!
Over here!
Talking to yourself? Huh?
What?!
I'm on the phone!
So you were lost in that,
weren't you?
Every young prince these days
sleeps and wakes up
with that thing in hand.
Put it away!
Who's this "young prince"?
- Prabhendu.
- Oh.
Indu looks radiant today.
Looks like he's met his maiden.
Indu!
It's Rupa.
He's probably calling me to the temple.
- Come on, let's go!
- Hey!
- Indu!
- Are you leaving?
Hey, Prabha...
your ticket to Bombay has arrived.
For Viraj Trivedi's recording session.
Aren't you coming to Bombay, Delulu?
Of course I am!
Anyway, I've got nothing else
to do here, right?
Hey...
When the flight is
up above the clouds,
will you be tempted
to go to heaven?
I'll save the rest of my laughter
for tomorrow!
Hey, your brother's calling.
Don't pick up!
That'll just bring trouble.
Must be because
I didn't enter the temple.
You're seeing a ghost this close...
Yet, why don't you believe in God?
The answer lies
within the question itself.
It's because I can't see God.
Can you see music, Prabha?
You can only hear music, right?
Yeah, I mean... we can play or sing.
That's just like taking a printout
from a printer.
But what I meant was...
the original source.
Music itself.
Where does music come from?
It's...
It's talent and practice.
Exactly!
Talent is God,
and practice is prayer!
Simple!
Incredible!
A devil is vouching for God!
Don't call me Devil!
I am a nice spirit!
A good soul.
Sorry, sorry!
I'm not entirely convinced
about you either, Delulu.
I keep calming myself down by thinking
you're nothing more than my imagination.
A very powerful and
impactful hallucination.
Oh Jesus!
So you're saying
my skills are worthless?
Ha! Skills?
You're still on a learner's permit!
You tried switching on the light
and blew the bulb!
Can you even touch anyone at all?
Pathetic!
Yes, I can.
Huh?!
This...
This breeze that hit me just now...
That was my touch.
Breeze is the easiest medium
to do that.
A soft breeze.
Give me the phone.
Let me see
if I can take a picture.
Go ahead.
You won't get anything.
Did it work?
Let me try a video.
Hmm.
Did it work now?
You won't see me in it.
Google Pay is risky.
Do you have cash?
Crush it properly,
mix it with water and have it.
Okay bro, thanks.
Huh?
- Hey!
- Where?
What is it?
Wait, we're coming.
Come on.
I'm screwed!
Come on, get up!
Let's go!
What's wrong?
I'll tell you later.
Let's go!
Hello... how high are you...
I mean... Hi... how are you?
What were you filming
on your phone?
No, I wasn't filming you guys!
He'll show it
to the cops, Sreerag.
Didn't we chase this guy off
the other day?
Don't you remember?
Boys, honestly,
I have nothing against you.
Give me your phone.
Don't give it to them, Prabha.
Let me deal with this.
You can check my gallery.
I haven't taken any pictures!
These guys are so rude, Prabha!
Grab the phone from him.
Just be quiet, Delulu!
- Huh?
Hit him, Prabha!
- Idiots!
- Delulu, please!
I can solve this!
What's wrong with this guy?
Just give me the phone, Kiddo.
I don't usually get involved
in things like these.
I don't even know
who you guys are.
How about I let you know?
Alright then.
Okay.
Let's go.
Sreerag...
Hey!
I just...
I got high all of a sudden.
- Is he gone?
- Yeah, perfect!
While you stood there like a tableau,
he walked off with the phone.
Huh? When?
Come on! If we hurry,
we can catch him.
Right!
Are they following us?
- Yes.
- Oh no!
They are just kids, Prabha.
This is bad,
this is really bad!
Stop for a second, Prabha.
Are you planning to spend your
whole life being scared like this?
Are you?
No.
Oh no!
Dude, go get him!
- Where's my bike key?
- Huh?
The bike key, where is it?
Can we talk after this?
Fine, fine.
Dude, don't leave!
Oh no!
- Hereafter...
- Hereafter?
- If you ever pull this kind of stunt--
- "on this street again..."
- I'll smash your face--
- "and change its shape," right?
- Yes!
- That's fine, Chetta. No problem.
- Hmm.
- Right.
Scram!
Oh, sorry, Chetta!
- All good?
- Absolutely!
Let's go!
What's the check-in time?
Ah... At 2:00 PM.
And the return flight?
That... we'll book that only
after tomorrow's recording.
Deepu Chetta, the reason I didn't
enter the temple yesterday...
It's not something
anyone should be forced to do.
It's your choice.
God is inside us, after all.
Temples and churches
are just like mirrors
that reflect that power.
Dad's a bit upset...
that even after taking up pujas,
I still avoid entering temples.
I've already talked to him
and sorted it out.
Dad knows very well how
sincerely you perform the pujas.
And that's why
your pujas are so effective.
Exactly!
Hey...
- What is it?
- Huh?
- What?
- Don't you hear a sound...
coming from the car?
- Really?
- Yes.
Oh, yeah.
You've got such sharp ears, Indu!
Looks like the car is due
for a service.
Yes, yes.
17-B
You can sit here, Prabha.
I'll be over there.
I was in Bangalore.
Yes. I was in Bangalore.
Did you board the wrong flight?
This flight is going to Mumbai.
Prabha! It's me, Delulu!
Huh?
But how? You've started
possessing people now?
How else can I talk to you?
This girl was a perfect fit.
Hmm! Your 'perfection'
is getting out of hand!
Yes, yes.
Prabha, listen.
I used to fly from Kochi
airport to Bangalore.
I'm very sure.
Did getting on the flight
trigger her memories?
Quick! Remember the rest.
Who was the one who said "Yes"?
Think quickly!
Even half of it is fine.
We'll figure out the rest
on the return flight.
Don't stress yourself.
Perhaps it will just come back
bit by bit.
Prabha...
I'm sensing something else too.
What is it?
Now that I've remembered
this one thing,
I feel much lighter.
It feels like a burden
has been taken off me.
That's a good thing, right?
Guess you're on your way
to salvation.
I think once you find out
who said that 'Yes,'
you'll move on for good.
Full free!
So you won't miss me if I go?
Ha, great!
Isn't it more important
that you get your freedom?
Salvation is important!
Wow!
So you won't miss me at all, huh?
Psst!
Yeah?
I'll miss you too.
What?!
I will miss you.
Psst! Prabha!
Sorry! I lost the connection.
Sorry, Madam.
- Creep!
- Yup!
I knew you'd miss me!
Hello?
No.
He's almost here.
I've packed all his things
in carton boxes.
His clothes, shoes, and books.
And the bluetooth
speaker he gifted me.
Hey, he's here.
I'll call you later.
Thanks, dear.
Hey...
Are you okay, Saadhya?
I'll be fine.
Don't worry.
These are your things.
Thanks.
- See, I--
- I'm getting late for work.
You take care, okay?
Enjoy New York.
Superb!
Didn't I tell you?
He is such a find, Saadhya!
Prabhendu, beautiful!
Please come here.
Thank you, sir.
She is the one who found you.
- Oh.
- Hi.
Saadhya.
Faizal keeps talking about you.
He's your biggest well-wisher, Prabhendu.
- Oh!
- Shift to Mumbai soon.
We need you here.
Sure, sir.
- Just a minute, Saadhya.
- Ah, sure, sir.
- Come on.
- Okay.
Good night, Prabhendu.
Until next time.
See you, sir.
See you.
I'm officially your fan, Prabha!
How do you play so well?
Well, that's just how talented I am!
Ugh!
Rupa has scheduled a puja
for tomorrow evening!
What do we do?
I've sent you the door password
for the service apartment.
The location too.
- It's close by.
- Got it.
Are you okay with the
evening flight tomorrow?
Err... is it possible to get a flight
that lands before noon tomorrow?
Ah... there's one at 6:30 AM.
Will that do?
I'm on that flight too.
Yeah, that's fine.
Okay.
Yes, it's okay.
You had dinner?
No.
Come on.
You can leave your bag here.
Okay.
Let's go.
We need to leave
for the airport at 4:30 AM.
- Okay.
- It'll be busy since it's the morning.
I brought my bags, thinking the
recording would go on all night.
You're amazing, Prabhendu!
You finished it so fast!
Pretty cool breeze, huh?
[mimicking Nivin Pauly]
Sorry.
She seems to be in
some kind of trouble.
I'll check.
Ugh! Classic heartbreak!
- Poor thing!
- Oh.
Aren't you eating?
Huh?
I asked...
aren't you eating?
Her boyfriend dumped her, Prabha.
Commitment issues.
Stop it, Delulu!
Poor girl. Still, she's handling
the situation so maturely.
Yeah.
Prabha, just ask her
if she's fine, no?
Uh... uh... uh...
What uh, uh, uh?
Don't just keep staring!
Say something!
Saadhya...
Aren't you eating
the bun and gravy?
Pav Bhaji.
Ah, Pav Bhaji.
Even though
I'm really angry with him...
he is actually a good guy.
My first instinct was to block him,
just like anyone would.
But then,
I decided to go through with it,
even though
it's a painful process.
It's better for getting
a proper closure.
Sometimes,
we can only blame the situation,
not the person.
If someone walks out of your life,
it's important to keep
your heart clear.
No anger, no grudges...
wishing only the best for them.
It's not easy.
But...
we get healed
just by being nice to them.
Prabha...
Are you able to see me?
Yeah.
I think I was in love.
I was in love with someone.
Do you remember his name?
So...
could he be the one
who said 'Yes'?
Then I should've been happy, right?
I didn't have to die!
Hello, sir.
Your friend has upgraded
you to an XL seat.
You can shift there
and sit more comfortably.
Thank you, sir.
Come.
Go on.
Won't this run?
It ran out of charge.
Uncle, you must've received an OTP.
Who are you calling "Uncle"?
Oh... sorry, bro.
An OTP must have come.
Could you tell me?
I've been sitting here for an hour.
I haven't seen anyone.
Prabhendu N. Namboothiri?
- Don't you have his number?
- I do.
Then just call and ask him.
Okay.
I thought you didn't believe
in ghosts and stuff.
- I don't believe in them, but I'm scared.
- Oh!
Aren't your mantras strong, sir?
Absolutely! A mantra saves
the one who chants it.
What was that line, Indu?
- A lie?
- Not a lie! A line!
Ah, it's
"Manana thraayathe ithi mantrah"
A doll!
Take the sacred ash.
Clean.
Let's go, let's go.
Wait, there's a guest room too.
- That's not really necess--
- Come on!
Clean!
Can we go now?
Close the window, Sashiyetta.
We don't want pigeons getting in.
Sir, next is the grandmother's room.
That's the main one.
You're not scared?
Of what?
You know plenty of mantras, right?
Chant them.
Come.
You too.
Who is he talking to?!
This is the grandmother's room.
After what happened,
not even the staff will enter here.
- She'd be in here all the time.
- Even now?
No, I mean before she died.
Okay.
She hardly slept.
Why are you telling me all this?
She really loved the balcony.
Why? Was she a smoker?
No, no.
To enjoy the breeze.
Shall we cleanse that area too?
Yeah! The balcony's safe.
There will be sunlight.
Open it! Open it!
Prabha!
What is it?
There...
Where?
- It's...
- What?
What?
What is it?
Don't kill us, sir!
We're not thieves, sir.
We were staying here
since it's an empty room.
- What?
- Is this the grandma?
Get out, you!
Oh no!
Don't call the police, Chetta!
Is the spirit gone?
Yes!
Clean!
Hey, did you decide to stop doing pujas
because of what happened today?
Not all all!
Today's puja worked, right?
We got rid of the spirit,
didn't we?
It's just that...
The thought of you not
being here with me anymore...
I'll be in Bombay from next week...
busy with stage shows
and practice sessions.
I can't commit to pujas
in the middle of all that.
It'll be a hassle for you too.
Hey!
Just leave the sacred
thread on for now.
Drop by when you're free.
I don't feel as scared
when you're with me.
Here, take this.
It's 50K.
50K? Wasn't our deal 60-40?
You take the whole thing.
Consider it your
provident fund!
Also, if you get any puja work
in Bombay, don't say no.
I've never been on a flight.
Get up! Let's go!
What?
Huh!
Hmm?
What?
- Oh no!
- What is it?
- Snake?
- A snake?
Get inside!
It's not safe, not safe!
Let's go.
Wow! Such a brave ghost!
One, two...
Three and four...
Guys, guys, guys!
I have to give the final count
for food tomorrow.
- Is anyone else coming?
- Yes.
There's one more person.
Veg.
- Hi, Prabhendu...
- Shall I book our tickets to Bombay
together for next week?
- With you on the flight,
I barely noticed we'd reached Kochi.
- Thanks for the company.
There's one more.
Play, play, play!
- Tomorrow evening is my
cousin's pre-wedding party.
- Just reminding you, since you said
you might come if you're free.
- I've sent the location.
What? Pookie Prabha
is feeling shy?
Why don't we go?
No, no, no.
You've got to play a little hard
to get, to be taken seriously.
Ugh!
When someone's being this frank,
don't put on
these stupid airs, okay?
I'm not putting on airs, Delulu.
I just feel weird when someone
gets close to me too quickly.
See... she just met us...
No, actually... sorry... met you.
Did she really have to tell you
her whole break-up story right away?
No.
I think she's into you.
No! It's...
Maybe it's just because
she cried in front of us.
Not just that!
Any other guy would have
used this chance to make a move.
And... don't think I'm saying this
to flatter you. But...
I think you are actually a nice guy.
Really?
Yeah!
In that case,
if I ask you something...
will you tell me the truth?
This is such a classic guy move!
When you're circling around for parking
and spot someone leaving a good space,
you just swoop straight in!
Love-sick fools!
Love?
And me?
Music is my only love!
Oh, spare me the drama!
Just leave music out of this.
And it's always the single guys
who are the most romantic!
Ugh!
What do you mean, "Ugh"?
Come here, Prabha.
Come here.
Sit down.
Prabha, a good relationship
just makes life better.
See... Someone who can understand
what's in your mind with a single glance...
And someone who can understand
the meaning of your silences.
Wouldn't it be great
to have that kind of support?
You're absolutely hell-bent on
making me park there, aren't you?
- Look, afterwards--
- That's not it.
Look, you'll be seeing
her again anyway.
So you'll have a good
friend in Mumbai.
We should go, Prabha.
It will be fun.
That place is on the outskirts.
Going by bike could be risky.
Why don't you take your dad's car?
Nah, that's not a good idea.
Why so much ego, Prabha?
It's not ego. It's just--
Is that Pappu?
Yes.
How did he get in?
No idea.
All done, Pappu.
If we don't let this wound heal,
the doctor will have to operate
on you again, just like last time.
Sleep now, okay?
Just call me
if you need anything.
Dad is right here, okay?
You haven't slept?
No.
Pappu has a wound on him.
If he remains outside,
flies will land on the wound,
and it'll end up getting infected.
I feel at peace
when he's in here.
When did you start this?
Two years ago.
It used to be a big cylinder.
Deepu brought this one.
It's comfortable.
Please put that spray bottle
in the cupboard.
Pappu might chew on it.
I haven't moved
any of your mom's belongings.
Thulasi washes them every week.
I press them
and put them back.
When I open that cupboard,
I feel like Sujatha is here,
even if just for a little while.
It gives me strength.
You can go to bed, Indu.
We are okay.
Dad...
Can I...
take our car tomorrow?
~ I saw you on the floor
In the crowd yet alone ~
~ The music in my heart
Rings the lub-dub tone ~
~ Would you let me
sing my love? ~
~ I drifted through the night
You're the star in my sight ~
~ The moment makes it right
For me and you ~
~ Would you let me
sing my love? ~
~ My heart snaps in two
Oh baby, looking at you ~
~ The music slows down
My sweetheart, dancing with you ~
~ As the new groom
arrives in splendid array ~
~ The whole place suddenly
glows in a lovely way ~
~ Like an ocean where
foaming waves lift and play ~
~ In this canopy decked
with garlands and bells ~
~ The colours now blossom
as beauty swells ~
~ Never to separate again ~
~ They must flow
through life's terrain ~
~ With one shared mind under the sun,
together... forever... as one ~
~ Smile and step where rhythms deploy,
ankle bells chiming in light convoy ~
~ O sparrows looping
in ecstatic ploy ~
~ Who is ready to dissolve
in that whirling joy? ~
~ In eyes lit bright where feelings beam,
there flickers softly a tender gleam ~
~ There's a tiny rattle
of naughty dreams that tattle ~
~ Yet no words can capture
such a dream ~
~ Without saying anything
to each other aloud ~
~ Through the sharpness of glances
their hearts have avowed ~
~ Will not all that's written
on life's turning page ~
~ Blossom forth as moonlight
that will never age? ~
~ Won't even their silence,
like a drifting cloud ~
~ Melt into honeyed words,
soft-falling, unbowed? ~
~ The umbrella is unfurling,
its shelter well dealt ~
~ And beneath its shade,
a calm is felt ~
~ Weaving a love as vast
as the ocean we span ~
~ Won't you and I rise
together like dawn... ~
~ Forever... as one? ~
~ I saw you on the floor
In the crowd yet alone ~
~ The music in my heart
Rings the lub-dub tone ~
~ Would you let me
sing my love? ~
~ In eyes lit bright where feelings beam,
there flickers softly a tender gleam ~
~ There's a tiny rattle
of naughty dreams that tattle ~
~ Yet no words can capture
such a dream ~
I need to tell you something, Prabha.
What is it?
I like you, Prabha.
Well...
I like you too, Delulu.
That's not what I meant.
I'm in love with you.
Thank you.
I love you too.
When I am speaking so frankly
without any ego,
why are you behaving like this?
When someone else showed up suddenly,
did I become nothing to you?
What's gotten into you, Delulu?
Weren't you the one who told me
to go meet Saadhya?
You're the one who set us up,
even after I said no.
Where did this love come from
all of a sudden,
like flipping a switch?
I don't know.
I don't know!
I can't hide things from the people
I care about the most.
I won't have any peace of mind.
And you're the only one I have!
I have no one else.
This is...
This is just a kind
of possessiveness.
You'll get over it.
Also,
even though you're a ghost,
you're not old enough
to get married.
And I'm almost past that age.
Prabha, stop calling me a "ghost"!
I've told you this many times.
Then what should I call you?
You don't know your name.
I can't even touch--
Prabha, love is not physical!
People love each other
from great distances.
People fall in love
even when they're much older.
It's about the deep
emotional connect we share.
We have that between us.
Can you honestly say
we don't have that?
That's not what I meant.
See...
I'm trying to be practical here.
When Saadhya hugged me today,
I felt my heart fill up.
It's the first time I've ever felt
something like that.
Today was the happiest
day of my life.
And you were the first person
I shared it with.
And now you've spoiled it!
You're so selfish!
You've changed so much, Prabha!
Your life has only gotten better
since I showed up, right?
I'm the reason
you even met Saadhya!
You are all the same!
All men are the same!
Answer the call.
I'm sorry.
Talk to her.
I need some privacy!
I'm the one who needs salvation...
from you!
What the hell, man?
Don't you have anything
better to do, you jerk?
Annie...
Our daughter has something to tell you.
I know what it is.
Not happening, Vinod.
Huh!
She wants a new iPhone, right?
She's making a habit of this.
No, Mom.
It's not about an iPhone!
- Then what?
- It's... well...
Papa, just tell her!
Mummy...
Chechi wants to
dye her hair blue.
Not blue, Chacko!
Lavender!
- Oh, so I have to say that too?
- Ugh!
Oh, Papa, just tell her
the main matter now!
What is it?
Well, Annie...
We're not just their parents.
We're their best friends too, right?
Skip the intro.
Get to the point.
Our daughter likes someone.
Oh, it's that Joe from Kottayam,
isn't it?
The moment I saw his gaze,
I knew it.
Eww! Joe and Aishu are already
in a relationship.
Huh! Since when?
Papa!
Okay. Straight to the point.
It's someone she met in Bangalore.
Not from college,
but through a mutual friend.
I warned you before,
many guys will come after you,
so watch out.
Annie, let me complete.
She's the one
who's going to propose!
Yes.
See, we're the first ones
she's telling this to.
I think we should appreciate that.
Yeah, we should.
He's coming tomorrow.
We'll just meet him, grab a coffee,
and head back.
That's it.
Does he like you?
He hasn't said so yet...
But I'm so sure... we have
a deep emotional connect.
Show me his photo.
See, Papa?
What did I say?
This is the problem with Mummy.
She judges instantly by looks!
Ha! We're meeting him tomorrow,
aren't we, Annie?
What's the harm in
showing a picture?
You don't like beards, Mummy.
He has a beard.
Also...
He is a Hindu.
And he's a little older than me.
Jesus!
Hey, relax!
Her prediction is that you'll be
the first one to like him, Annie!
Let us go, Mummy.
Chechi will be happy.
- "Us"? No way!
- Huh?
You've got school tomorrow morning!
Your Papa and I
will meet him first.
- Yeah! Yaay!!
- Success!
I'll show you, okay?
I'm sure you'll be happy.
Promise?
Promise.
You know Varkey, right?
He runs the coffee shop here.
His cold coffee is
already famous, Annie.
Where is he?
He's late.
He needs time to get here, Mummy.
What is it?
Dear...
Papa, one sec.
He's not coming, right?
Yeah, he's not coming.
Are you happy now, Mummy?
Sorry, Papa.
I think he guessed it.
He guessed
why I asked him to come.
That's okay, dear.
It's alright.
We shouldn't expect anything
from anyone.
Your generation generally has a hesitation
to become committed.
It's quite natural, dear.
How can you judge someone
you don't even know, Mummy?
Papa, I think he is just confused.
Maybe it'll be fine
if I just talk to him.
Dear!
Rakhi, please ask the Head Boy
to come to my office.
Good afternoon, Ma'am.
Good afternoon.
Jacob V. Manjooran from 8-C...
His sister had an accident.
She's in critical condition.
Avinash, I need you to go with him
to the hospital.
I'll have a staff member
go with you.
- Okay, Ma'am.
- Jacob's parents will be there.
Till then, make sure that he's fine.
Sure, Ma'am.
She's in the ICU.
Third floor.
Papa...
Where is Chechi?
Chacko...
Do you know when your sister
was her happiest?
When you were born,
on the floor right below us.
To make your Chechi happy now,
Papa needs your help
with something.
The doctors are saying...
that your sister is gone.
Her brain is dead.
To stop the machine support...
and set her free...
they need my permission.
They need a... "Yes" from me.
But...
unless... unless you also say "Yes"...
I won't say "Yes."
If I say "Yes"...
will Chechi be happy?
Yes.
Promise?
Promise.
Yes!
My Papa's name is
Vinod Mathew Manjooran.
We have a plantation.
Magic Hills Plantation.
It's in Kuttikkanam.
My Mummy's name is Annie.
Chacko's real name is Jacob.
Same name as my grandfather.
What's your name?
Delulu.
That's just the name
we gave you, right?
What's your real name?
Delulu...
means delusion...
means Maya.
Maya Mathew.
~ Don't leave; don't make my eyes
turn to tears ~
~ Don't disappear and fill my heart
with painful spears ~
~ Wasn't it in your eyes
that I saw myself clearer ~
~ As though I stood
before a living mirror? ~
~ When I stood all alone
in silent plea ~
~ Didn't you arrive
and breathe life into me? ~
~ As I climbed the steps
where darkness spread ~
~ To sparkle and shine
in the path ahead ~
~ You appeared as a star in golden frame,
you rose as a lamp with a steady flame ~
~ You flew from the sky
and landed with art ~
~ Resting gently
on the branch of my heart ~
~ O petal, O angel,
sweet counterpart ~
~ O magic unending,
eternally rare ~
~ May you never
disappear anywhere ~
~ O magic unending,
eternally rare ~
~ May you never
disappear anywhere ~
~ Don't leave; don't make my eyes
turn to tears ~
~ Don't disappear and fill my heart
with painful spears ~
~ The memories simply soak
in the rain of sorrow's tears ~
~ And in that rain your face appears,
whispering its stories to my ears ~
~ The summer of separation
scorches everything in sight ~
~ And in that heat, thoughts of you
smoulder like an ember bright ~
~ O smile that enfolds me
in wings of feathered gleam ~
~ Do not fade like an unseen wind
lost in a dream ~
~ You flew from the sky
and landed with art ~
~ Resting gently
on the branch of my heart ~
~ O petal, O angel,
sweet counterpart ~
~ O magic unending,
eternally rare ~
~ May you never
disappear anywhere ~
~ O magic unending,
eternally rare ~
~ May you never
disappear anywhere ~
Indu...
Everything you said
could be your imagination,
or it could be true.
I'd like to believe
that it's true.
Her parents haven't seen
the person she loved, till date.
A soul can find
peace and salvation
only by freeing itself
from sorrow!
Lakshmy, the guest room first.
Okay, Madam.
- Would this do?
- Yes.
Yes?
I'm a friend of Maya's.
I was in the area
and thought I'd drop by.
Oh.
Come in.
Maya always used to say...
that regardless of how much
you both fought,
when she was away,
the one she missed the most...
was her mom.
She's a big liar.
She'd say the exact same thing
about her Papa.
We still haven't been able
to accept that reality
So, we don't really...
miss her, as such.
Her Papa has turned
into a complete workaholic.
And Chacko keeps studying
all the time.
He's even the class topper now.
But there are two things
that really trouble me.
I miss her whenever I open
the fridge in the kitchen.
She always used to walk over
and open the fridge,
ever since she was a little girl.
And then, when I see clothes
lying all over the bed.
No matter how many times I told her,
she always left her clothes on the bed.
Clothes were her weakness.
She was always on her phone,
browsing for them.
Let me get you
something to drink.
"You don't like beards, Mummy."
"He has a beard."
"And..."
"He is a Hindu."
"And he's a little older than me."
What's your name?
Prabhendu.
You were the one she was in love with...
Isn't that right, Prabhendu?
Yes.
~ When someone sat close to me at night,
like new-fallen rain in cool delight ~
~ My heart shifted, lighter than ever,
turning at once to a moonlit river ~
~ Slowly unfolding its wings
in tender delight ~
~ Weaving a chain of laughter
pure and bright ~
~ My mind fills up
on its own tonight ~
~ Come, let's go to distances
we've never seen ~
~ Becoming two lovely,
colourful clouds serene ~
~ In this new birth
where our paths convene ~
~ Let's find our shelter on a blossom
branch kissed by morning dew ~
~ Becoming the breath
that rises soft and true ~
~ Till every painful memory
softens and bids adieu ~